Kelly Swisher, an Arkansas woman, escaped injury and managed to safely stop her car
after a four -foot -long rat snake came out from under her car seat.
after a four -foot -long rat snake came out from under her car seat and slid across
her feet as she was driving down the highway.
Rat snakes aren't poisonous or a threat to people generally and slid across her feet
as she was driving down the highway.
Rat snakes aren't poisonous or a threat to people generally but the woman says the
snake she encountered Thursday terrified her out of her It was rough with big
scales, said Swisher,
but the woman says the snake she encountered Thursday terrified her out of her wits.
Who was on her way to pick up her friend at the airport when it happened?
I don't know whether I had my hands on the steering wheel or not.
I am not the most flexible person in the world, but I can guarantee my knees were up
next to my ears.
She said the snake first slid back under the seat.
I am not the most flexible person in the world,
but I can guarantee my knees were up next to my ears.